{
    "subject": "resource/10_Questions_for_the_Dalai_Lama",
    "predicate": "property/cinematographer",
    "object": "Rick Ray",
    "human_readable": "The cinematographer of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' is Rick Ray.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752253890037537,
            "question": "Who is the cinematographer of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8519792556762695,
            "question": "Where was '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8386369943618774,
            "question": "Describe the visual style of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7567745447158813,
            "question": "What film did Rick Ray work on as a cinematographer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7446070909500122,
            "question": "What is the genre of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6651957631111145,
            "question": "What year was '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4824294149875641,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Rick Ray."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47449615597724915,
            "question": "Is Rick Ray known for his work in documentary filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4152606725692749,
            "question": "Has Rick Ray won any awards for his cinematography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28375759720802307,
            "question": "What other projects has Rick Ray been involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The cinematographer of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' is Rick Ray.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3710_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Rick Ray won any awards for his cinematography?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3710_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Rick Ray known for his work in documentary filmmaking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3710_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Rick Ray.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3710_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3710_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it states that Rick Ray is the director/writer/cinematographer/editor/producer of the documentary \"10 Questions for the Dalai Lama\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Rick Ray is the director, writer, cinematographer, editor, and producer of the documentary \u201c10 Questions for the Dalai Lama,\u201d which confirms that Rick Ray is indeed the cinematographer of this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}